Reach your hands out,
cut through the wind,
and forge ahead, drawing your own map as you go!
We can't even tell left from right
in this tempest-tossed era
Even the values we've honed
seem ready to crumble
Is the compass leading us true,
or is it leading us astray?
Nobody knows for sure!
Just breathe deep, close your eyes
and you'll find your soul guiding the way!
Reach your hands out,
cut through the wind,
and kick away the darkness!
I'm doing this for myself,
and you're doing this for yourself too, right?
Forge ahead, painting the world in your own colors!
I'm gonna roast ya!
Til you're well-done!
Gonna mince ya!
Please take me straight to the castle!
What's the matter, Izo,
making me carry an injured man?
Sorry.
But that earlier news...
...about a giant specter appearing
on the second floor caused me some alarm.
Yeah, where'd it even come from?
I heard the castle is ablaze.
Don't let up then, yeah?
Aye!
Get moving!
The monster's coming!
Those damn samurai
are blocking the exit!
Cannon... Bring a cannon!
The castle's a living hell!
Secure an exit!
Stupid samurai...
kick their asses!
Get outta here, or we're all toast!
It's a great deal for ya,
Young Master Yamato!
Just hear me oooout!
Apoo, at it again!
And now you're thinking you're going to
gain favor with Yamato, are you?!
I'm talkin' to you,
Young Master!
Stop, Apoo!
I told you, I am occupied!
Do not follow me!
Fuga!
It has been a while...
But I am pressed for time!
Now is not the time
for frolicking around...
Castle Second Floor to all floors:
The giant flaming specter
is headed underground!
Hm? A cushion?
No, this is...
...a head of hair.
Whose, though?!
Here they come!
Indeed.
You cannot run!
Fight it is, then!
Eh?
What... is that?!
A ball of flame?
A nuisance...
What's that?!
So huuuuge!
The flame specter's intentions
remain unknown!
Fuga, run! It comes!
The flame specter is descending!
I repeat:
It is descending!
Is that what happens...
...when he pulls on his crest?!
What the hell is he up to?
Imperial Deep Pride...
...Stake!
Is it unblockable?!
It's basically a damn laser!
In ancient times,
this is how the pteranodon...
...hunted its prey!
Dammit, didn't know that!
I've gotta land a hit on him somehow,
or all I'm gonna do is tire myself out!
Don't tell me that flame on his back
also comes with being a pteranodon!
It doesn't!
Who does he think he is,
talking to me from up there!
First things first:
knock him out of the sky!
Three-Sword Style:
Kalasutra:
Grand Dragon Twister!
What the hell is up with this guy's
weird-ass toughness?!
Guess dragons and dinos both
soak up damage like nobody's business, huh?
That's right.
But in my case, it goes even beyond that.
You could say I'm a little unique.
I'll give you the
sword fight you want!
I like swords, too.
I've slashed him
more than a few times.
Ultra...
Tiger Hunt!
But he ain't bleeding.
He can flap his wings.
They're not just for show,
but I can't be sure he can fly with them.
The flame on his back
is still burning...
Thought that was part of
his Devil Fruit power, but guess not.
Maybe he's got Fishman
or Giant's blood in him?
Guess it's some race
I've never heard of...
You're searching for answers...
Your eyes betray your confusion!
If this keeps up...
...and I can't figure out what he is...
I don't think...
...can...
...beat him.
What's that sound?
A shamisen? Ain't no way...
The hell is happening?!
Enma's...!
What is this?
The sound of a shamisen?
Impossible...
In the midst of battle?
What trickery is this?!
Is it coming from
the room next door?
I-Is it the enemy?
Who is it?
No one could possibly
be holding a feast right now...
It's so bright...
I can't see...
Ko... Komu...
Komurasaki!
Is this the afterlife?
Or is this a dream?
Since that day, not a night has passed
that I don't dream about you.
How could I possibly forget you!
I cannot forget you, either...
...milord.
Tam, and always shall be,
by your side.
If this is a dream,
I don't want to wake up!
What is that?!
It passes through the walls!
To the abyss...
Shoot, shoot!
I repeat, Castle Second Floor
to all floors:
The flame specter continues
its descent underground!
"Descent"?!
That mustn't happen!
If it keeps descending,
it will reach the armory!
Should that come to pass,
it will ignite
the massive pile of gunpowder!
I must hurry!
Fuga!
I want you to help me
with something!
This way!
Come with me!
Whoa!
What I would give for a moment's respite
upon this wonderful, soft bed,
but we ought to be off.
The CPo agents are
just beyond the flames!
And they'll be after us before we know it!
Let's not tarry, then!
Nico Robin...
You cannot run from us...!
Smile! I'm taking
a commemorative photo for you!
"Pets of the Celestial Dragons
at Kaido's Castle!"
This's a scoop!
Maybe I'll sell this story to Morgans,
from the World Economic Journal!
I can see the headlines now:
"The Government, After Losing
Their Broker Doflamingo,
Finally..."
Hey! Apoo?!
X. Drake...
Do you think we don't know
who you really are?
Go ahead, try coming up
with a cover story!
Inconveniences...
...must be erased.
Boom!
Dammit!
That hurt, you stupid ass
Government assassins!
Oh, you're alive.
Shaddap!
What, ya think I wouldn't
use Armament Haki, dumbass?!
I'll make them pay for that!
And you're Navy, aren't ya?!
Mouth shut.
Are we doing this or not?
Well, they started it!
No, you did.
We're absolutely doing this!
Why's it suddenly...?!
Enma!
Who said you could
unleash yourself without my permission?!
What's wrong?
Having a falling out?
Nuh?!
What're you trying now?!
I'll give you a chance.
Do what you want.
Don't you look down on me!
Direct hit!
Huh?!
That was the Pirate Hunter
you had on the Snail, wasn't it?!
Ain't no way
he's winnin' against King!
Close call...
If my Color of Arms was any slower,
I would've been toast...
From the size of that blast,
it was almost like he was trying to kill both of us!
How in the hell
is he still alive?!
That was a straight-up suicide attack!
He's one of the last remaining Lunarians,
a survivor of a race thought to be wiped out!
A race of monsters,
able to survive in any environment!
Long ago, folks called 'em "gods"!
How'd they end up wiped out?
Huh?! That's something...
...you oughta look up
in a history book!
One-Sword Style, Draw:
Death...
...Lion Song!
Not even a damn scratch?!
That attack was way stronger
than the others!
A shamisen?
Whoa, wait, Enma!
Imperial Deep Pride Stake!
Not now, Enma!
First time I've seen a swordsman
held back by his own sword!
Kitetsu III!
A cursed sword, huh?!
YYou idiot,
it ain't for sale!
If you die using it,
it'd be like I done the deed myself!
How 'bout this, then?
I'm taking it.
My, how Kitetsu's countenance
has changed!
It would seem it has finally found
the hands of a worthy owner!
The Kitetsu III you wield
is of my design.
That true?!
You going to die,
just to save your sword?
Hot!
Oh, good. It didn't fall off.
Wado Ichimonji...
Sensei!
Let me have her sword!
Aye, very well.
I'm gonna get stronger,
for both of us!
I'm gonna get so strong,
the heavens'll know my name!
I'm gonna be
the world's strongest swordsman!
Boy!
Enma, the blade Hiyori-sama
bestowed upon you...
Does it perhaps feel
strangely familiar in your grasp?
It works much like
any cursed blade.
The weak cannot handle them.
But the most important reason
it has molded itself to your hand, by twist of fate,
is that Wado Ichimonji and Enma
were forged by the same person!
The artisan,
Shimotsuki Kozaburo!
It all happened so fast,
I never really stopped to think about it...
But how'd a sword from Wano...
...end up in the backwaters
of the East Blue?
Completed your three-sword set?
Imperial Slings and Arrows!
Enma!
Enma...
A sword from the Land of Wano...
A sword from Wano!
Zorojuro.
The word "Sunacchi"...
I was warned to never say it.
learned it from an old man in my village
a long time ago.
Never said it, either.
What?!
An old man in the village?!
That old man
who was always on the sea coast...
For the longest time,
I didn't know his name.
Not there!
Go, go!
That's the spirit, Zoro!
Sunacchi!
'Tis a word for good luck,
raises the spirit!
Huh...
I dun need it.
Funny word.
Anyway, old man,
you were a Samurai, weren'tcha?
Everyone at the dojo said so.
Best they hold their tongues!
Lest the Navy be upon us.
The Navy?! Why?!
I will not say!
Off with ye, damned brat!
What's your problem,
ya stubborn old fart?!
Does the dojo bore you?
lost to Kuina again!
I gotta practice more!
Huh?!
I don't got money to pay with, though!
They are yours.
Blunt as they are, though.
I...
...cannot seem to forge
anything but junk in my old age.
Use them for your training.
Listen, now.
A sword is like a kitchen knife,
but for murder!
They are designed to kill people!
A swordsmith hones their craft so that their weapons
are better at killing than any other!
Every sword possesses
its own personality;
'tis a swordsman's lot to tame it!
And they label dangerous
swords "cursed?!
Ridiculous!
That is the hallmark of a fine sword!
If the weak fear it
and deem it "cursed,"
it is rather...
...an honor!
Swords are fearsome...
...because they yearn
so deeply to be deadly!
There was one I forged
when I was young...
And it was my greatest
stroke of genius...
The sword had
a serious temperament!
'Twas such a fine blade,
it gave you chills merely from holding it...
And to it, I gave the name of
hell's mighty king!
Hell's mighty king...
Enma!
My village was named Shimotsuki...
Guess it wasn't a coincidence...
On the day that old man died,
learned...
...that he was Kuina's grandfather.
Catch me if you want
this Excellent Grade Sword back!
That's just a bamboo sword!
Give it back, darn it!
Hey, guys! Did you know?!
My grandma said this village
was founded by a pirate!
Whaaaa!!
A pirate...
The artisan,
Shimotsuki Kozaburo!
More than half a century ago,
he unlawfully emigrated from this country.
That old man was a samurai
from the Land of Wano?!
The swordsmith,
Shimotsuki Kozaburo!
Finer swords closely observe humans!
They select their swordsmen!
They say the sword chooses the owner.
You came to me...
...because you chose me,
you wanted to test me...
A sword is honest, direct...
Not evil.
That means it's my strength
that's lacking!
So does this mean that
even with you draining a ton of Haki,
Oden wielded you like
you were light as a feather?
Am I right, Enma?
There he is!
It's Pirate Hunter Zoro!
And he's all beat up!
King-san!
Let us take his head!
If we beat him, we'll get promoted!
Me! I'll do it!
What do I do...
...to keep my Haki in balance?
I'm dead if I keep releasing
this much Haki...
NO...
I'm fine with that!
I see...
Looking to become a king?
That sounds great!
The world's greatest swordsman?
The Pirate King won't settle
for anything less!
That's right.
'Cause I've got...
...promises to keep...
...to my captain,
and to my best friend!